I have a daughter and uh everybody
always says my daughter looks just like
me when she gets older that's going to
be really
depressing thing I learned about having
kids is anywhere you go they always want
you to buy him a toy and the other thing
I learned about my daughter is she hates
going to the doctor because a while back
she had to get some shots so even the
thought of go to the doctor like she
completely pitches a fit and that's why
I think they should give shots at the
toy store
no day I don't want to get to the toy
store
anymore that's okay you don't have to
yes better yet maybe they could give
those shots at
McDonald's administered by Elmo
and maybe they could have Elsa from the
movie Frozen hold him
down no Daddy I don't want to watch no
more Frozen
anymore that's okay you don't have to
yes she also likes to sing but since
she's so young she doesn't always get
the words right like for a while she
thought that Mary had a little man
I'm like if his flee is as wet as snow
it's probably Papa
Smurf she also has those shoes that
light up which is great till you're
driving and she's in the back seat and
you think you're getting pulled over by
a
[Laughter]
cop wow back we were in the car and she
was in the back seat she's like M Daddy
this is a really good burger I'm like
where did you get a
burger from my
nose sorry that really happened and I'm
a comedian
so thing about my daughter she loves to
watch the Disney Channel and what's
crazy is like she'll learn these words
she has no idea what they mean but it's
crazy CU she'll use them in the right
context like give you an example I was
running a joke by a comedian friend of
mine and he did not laugh at all and
without missing a beat my daughter's
like
awkward I think I just got heckled my my
own
daughter wasn't the first time I was on
my on my way out the door to an event
and my daughter's like Daddy be funny
I'm like Ella I always am she's like you
never
[Laughter]
know thing about my daughter though is
she is really lazy she doesn't like to
do chores pick up her toys so if I had
to do it all over again I would name her
faith that way when she decided not to
do her chores or pick up her toys I just
open up the Bible to James 21:17 and be
like look right there it says faith
without works is dead
o
[Music]